Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Municipal Governments, 1929-1975; II.
  - Greensburg, "The 1961 Budget Review of Financial Operations at Mid-Year and Projection for the Year", August, 1961
  - Greensburg, "Budget Review and Projection 1960", May, 1960
  - Greensburg, "An Outline of the Accounting System of the City of Greensburg", July, 1956
  - Greensburg, "Greensburg City Finances 1952-1957", May, 1957
  - Greensburg, "A 1950 Budget Review and a Look at Some Future Financial Problems", August, 1950
  - Greensburg, "A Mid-Year Look at 1964 Finances", July, 1964
  - Greensburg, "1965 Finances at Mid-Year", July, 1965
  - Greensburg, "1948 Fiscal Operation and the 1949 Budget City of Greensburg", May, 1949
  - Greensburg, "Greensburg City's 1949 Finances at Mid-Year", July, 1949
  - Greensburg, "Proposed Schedule of Future Sinking Fund Operations", March, 1949
  - Greensburg, "Memorandum on Refuse Collection and Incineration", March, 1949
  - Greensburg, "Greensburg's 1948 Budget at Mid-Year", July, 1948
  - Greensburg, "1947 Fiscal Operations and the 1948 Budget City of Greensburg", April, 1948
  - Greensburg, "Seven Months of Greensburg 1947 Budget", August, 1947
  - Greensburg, "Greensburg City Finances in 1946 and 1947 a Budgetary Review", March, 1947
  - Greensburg, "Ten-Month Review of the 1946 Budget", December, 1946
  - Greensburg, "Report on the Bonded Debt and Sinking Fund with a Financial Improvement Plan", July, 1946
  - Greenville, "Merger Considerations Greenville-Hempfield", July, 1962
  - Greenville, "Position Classifications of Borough Employees", March, 1963
  - Greenville, "A Financial Survey of Greenville, Pennsylvania Volume I An Eighteen Year Financial History", April, 1947
  - Greenville, "Greenville-Hempfield Financial Analysis", May, 1961
  - Greenville, "A Survey of the Local Parking Problem", February, 1951
  - Greenville, "A Self-Administered Police Pension Plan", May, 1958
  - Greenville, "A Survey on the Volunteer Fireman as a Means of Strengthening the Greenville Fire Department", April, 1956
  - Greenville, "Greenville-Hempfield Merger Study Part I: Township of Hempfield Fiscal Analysis: 1964-1967, 1969-1973", August, 1968
  - Greenville, "Greenville-Hempfield Merger Study Part II: Borough of Greenville Fiscal Analysis: 1964-1967, 1969-1973", March, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Greenville, "Greenville-Hempfield Merger Study Exhibits ONLY for Part II: Borough of Greenville Fiscal Analysis: 1964-1967, 1969-1973", March, 1969
  - Greenville, "Greenville-Hempfield Merger Study Part III: Legal Implications of Merger", August, 1969
  - Greenville, "Proposed Compensation Plan", May, 1980
  - Grove, "A Self-Administered Police Pension Plan", December, 1960
  - Grove, "$75,000 of Bonds Series of September, 1975", August, 1957
  - Grove, "Space Utilization Alternatives for the Grove City Hospital Part I: In-House Laundry verse Contracted-Out Laundry Service", May, 1968
  - Grove, "Personnel Classification Revision", March, 1975
  - Grove, "A Survey of the Accounting System", June, 1949
  - Grove,"A Study of Downtown Parking Facilities", April, 1955
  - Grove, "A Study to Help Grove City Solve its Fringe Problems", September, 1955
  - Grove, "A Study to Determine the Future Operation of the Grove City Electric Plant", October, 1958
  - Grove, "Study of the Proposed Annexation of Area Known as Hallville", February, 1950
  - Grove, "A Comprehensive Salary and Wage Schedule for Grove City Borough Employees", October, 1962
  - Grove, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan", November, 1960
  - Glassport, "Preliminary Fiscal Analysis", March, 1963
  - Glassport, "Police Pension Fund Self-Administered", December, 1958
  - Glassport, "Financial Analysis Borough of Glassport 1962-1966", December, 1967
  - Hampton, "The Fiscal Posture of Hampton Township Past, Present, and Future", May, 1965
  - Hampton, "A Review and Projection of Hampton Township's Fiscal Status 1971-1979", September, 1976
  - Hampton, "Preliminary Operating Study of Hampton Township", March, 1952
  - Harrisburg, "Investment of Municipal Funds in Pennsylvania", September, 1962
  - Harrisburg, "The Fiscal Posture of Harrison Township: A Three-Year Review and a Look at the Immediate Future", December, 1970
  - Harrisburg, "Increased Fire Protection for Harrisburg", August, 1951
  - Harrisburg, "A Program for Rehabilitating Harrisburg's Streets", August, 1948
  - Harrisburg, "Ash and Rubbish Collection in the City of Harrisburg", August, 1948
  - Hazleton, "Status of Hazleton City Finances as of October 1, 1957", November, 1957
  - Hazleton, "Hazleton City Finances First Quarter 1958", May, 1958
  - Hazleton, "Hazelton City Finances as of June 30, 1958", July,1958
  - Hempfield, "Hempfield Township Report on a Survey of Business Administration and Accounting Procedures", August, 1964
  - Hempfield, "Financial Analysis of Hempfield Township", May,1945
  - Hempfield, "Financial Analysis of Hempfield Township 1945-1951", March, 1952
  - Hermitage, "The Cost of Tax Collection: A Procedural/Cost Analysis of Tax Collection in the Municipality of Hermitage", June, 1983
  - Hickory, "A Proposed Sewer Rate for the Township of Hickory", September, 1967
  - Hickory, "A Report on Hickory Township 1958 Fiscal Operation", January, 1959
  - Hickory, "Hickory Township Police Pension Plan", March, 1958
  - Hickory, "A Survey of the Hickory Township Sanitary District #1", August, 1946
  - Hickory, "Report on Hickory Township Sewage Study", November, 1954
  - Hickory, "A Report on Hickory Township 1958 Fiscal Operation", January, 1959
  - Hickory, "Sewage Disposal Control in Hickory Township", August, 1954
  - Hollidaysburg, "Financial Operations of the Borough of Hollidaysburg-1955- and the 1956 Budget", October, 1956
  - Hollidaysburg, "A Financial Analysis of the Borough of Hollidaysburgh 1941-1949 and the Budget for 1950", August, 1950
  - Hollidaysburg, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications: Phoenix Volunteer Fire Company", February, 1975
  - Homestead, "A Financial Appraisal of the Borough of Homestead for the Years 1939-1944", December, 1944
  - Homestead, "Homestead Borough Financial Analysis" 1939 – 1944" 1945
  - Homestead, "Financial Analysis Borough of Homestead", 1946
  - Hopewell, "Survey of Police Department Requirements", October, 1968
  - Hopewell, "Alternative Methods of Refuse Collection", June, 1968
  - Hopewell, "Hopewell Township a Report on 1956 Financial Operations and the 1957 Budget", June, 1957
  - Indian, "Indian Borough – A Financial Analysis of the Past and a Look at the Future", December, 1965
  - Indian, "A Simplified Accounting System (Including Budgetary Controls)", June, 1959
  - Ingram, "A Financial Analysis of Ingram Borough 1940-1949 the 1950 Budget and Looking Ahead to 1951", June, 1950
  - Irwin, "Municipal Employe Retirement Systems", November, 1962
  - Irwin, "An Administrative Survey of the Government of the Borough of Irwin, Pennsylvania", June, 1965
  - Irwin, "Survey of the Parking Problem in the Borough of Irwin", May, 1953
  - Irwin, "Financial Survey Borough of Irwin", October, 1958
  - Irwin, "The Financial Picture and an Improvement Program," January, 1955
  - Irwin, "Debits and Credits in Municipal Consolidation", November, 1964
  - Irwin, "An Analysis of Parking Patterns and Problems in the Central Business District", January, 1975
  - Jamestown, "Administrative Analysis: Borough of Jamestown Part II: Fiscal and Administrative Analysis of the Jamestown Borough Government", December, 1974
  - Jeannette, "Report on Garbage and Rubbish Collection for the City of Jeannette (Revised)", March, 1949
  - Jeannette, "Ten years of Municipal Finance in a Ten Year old City 1937-1946", August, 1947 (Box 16)
  - Jeannette, "Report on Garbage and Rubbish Collection for the City of Jeannette", June, 1943
  - Jeannette, "Proposed Firemen's Pension Plan", August, 1975
  - Jeannette, "Police Pension Plan", March, 1969
  - Jeannette, "A Position Salary Survey", February, 1962
  - Jeannette, "Job Classification Study", January, 1965
  - Jeannette, "Financial Trends 1950-1962", June, 1962
  - Jeannette, "The 1963 Financial Budget and 1962 Financial Operations", May, 1963
  - Jeannette, "A Financial Predicament", March, 1955
  - Jeannette, "A Program of Street Improvements", August, 1952
  - Jeannette, "The Problem of Street Improvements", June, 1956
  - Jeannette, "Recommendations Relating to an Accounting System", March, 1958
  - Jeannette, "Recommendations Relating to an Accounting System Volume II: Exhibits and Forms", March, 1958
  - Jeannette, "Study of Jeannette Fire Department", July, 1957
  - Jeannette, "A Study of Downtown Parking Facilities", September, 1954
  - Johnstown, "Enrollment Trends and Projections: The Greater Johnstown Area Vocational Technical School and the Seven School Districts of the AVTS Attendance Area", August, 1976
  - Johnstown, "Economic Survey for the Central Business District", February, 1962
  - Johnstown, "Confidential Report on the Preliminary Financial Study of the City of Johnstown 1938 to 1947 and 1948 Budget", November, 1948
  - Johnstown, "Report on the Financial Study of the City of Johnstown – 1948 to 1954", May, 1955
  - Johnstown, "Guidelines for Fiscal Planning", July, 1970
  - Johnstown, "Proposed Pay Plan for the City of Johnstown", April, 1962
  - Johnstown, "Fiscal and Administrative Study Volume I Report in Brief and an Administrative Analysis", November, 1961
  - Johnstown, "Fiscal and Administrative Study Volume II A Review of the City Finances", November, 1961
  - Johnstown, "Fiscal and Administrative Study Volume III Position Classification Study", November, 1961
  - Jefferson, "Preliminary Study on the Effects of Jointure of the Present Member Districts of the Perry-Lower Tyrone Joint School System and Jefferson Township School District", March, 1961
  - Jefferson, "Study of the Proposed Annexation of Area Surrounding Jefferson", November, 1956
  - Kennett Square, "Position Classification and Pay Plan for the Borough of Kennett Square", September, 1966
  - Kittanning, "Kittanning Borough's Fiscal Picture: The League Reviews the 1961 Financial Operations and 1962 Budget of the Borough of Kittanning", November, 1962
  - Kittanning, "Kittanning Borough Maintains a Sound Financial Program: A Review of the 1963 Financial Operations and 1964 Budget of the Borough of Kittanning", October, 1964
  - Kittanning, "A Study of the Proposed Consolidation of the Boroughs of Applewold, Kittanning and West Kittanning", July, 1961
  - Kittanning, "A Re-Examination of the Police Pension Plan", November, 1967
  - Kittanning, "The League Studies the Financial Impact of the Renewal Project in the First Ward of the Borough of Kittanning", December, 1964
  - Kittanning, "A Survey of Parking and Traffic Conditions in the Business District of Kittanning Borough", October, 1954
  - Kittanning, "Occupation Privilege Tax: A Comparison of Two Model Ordinances Suggested Forms and Accounting Procedures to be Used for the Occupation Privilege Tax in Kittanning Borough", April, 1965
  - Kittanning, "Kittanning Borough Occupation Privilege Tax Model Occupation Privilege Tax Collection Forms and Accounting Procedures", June, 1965
  - Kittanning, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Kittanning Borough 1966-1976", November, 1971
  - Kittanning, "A Study of Borough Parking Facilities", August, 1968
  - Lakemont Park, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications Lakemont Park", October, 1981
  - Lancaster City, "Lancaster City General Fund Budget Review", December, 1959
  - Lancaster City, "Lancaster City Finances 1948-1957", September, 1958
  - Lancaster City, "General Fund Budget Review", December, 1958
  - Lancaster City, "The Location of Fire Stations in the City of Lancaster", December, 1949
  - Latrobe, "Fiscal Analysis of Latrobe Borough 1966-1971", December, 1972
  - Latrobe, "Solid Waste Collection Procedures", October, 1975
  - Latrobe, "The Parking Violation Ticket", May, 1962
  - Latrobe, "Financial Budgets 1961 Results and 1962 Outlook", March, 1962
  - Latrobe, "Twenty Years and an Outlook 1945-1970", August, 1964
  - Latrobe, "Report on Accounting Records and Control", November, 1943
  - Latrobe, "A Financial Plan for Latrobe", 1943
  - Latrobe, "Changing he Form of Government", June, 1967
  - Latrobe, "Financial Trend 1955-1961 Borough of Latrobe", May, 1961
  - Latrobe, "Financial Trends Borough of Latrobe 1946-1961", April, 1956
  - Latrobe, "Some Problems Relating to Sewage Treatment and Disposal", February, 1954
  - Lebanon City, "The 1961 Lebanon City Budget a League Review", February, 1961
  - Lebanon City, "Job Classification and Pay Plan", December, 1964
  - Leechburg, "A Study of Downtown Parking Facilities", October, 1955
  - Leechburg, "Police Pension Plan Self-Administered", September, 1958
  - Leechburg, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Borough of Leechburg 1965-1974", August, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Leechburg, "Preliminary Survey 1971 Proposed Budget", December, 1970
  - Liberty, "Financial and Operating Review 1941-1949 Actual and 1950 Budget", January, 1951
  - Liberty, "An Operation Study of the Water Department", April, 1951
  - Liberty, "Preliminary Budget – 1959", February, 1959
  - Liberty, "A Study of Procedures and Proposals for Incorporation", December, 1961
  - Ligonier, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Ligonier Borough 1965-1975", June, 1971
  - Ligonier, "A Traffic and Parking Survey", December, 1956
  - Ligonier, "An Analysis of the Economic Factors Involved with Borough Incorporation for Laurel Mountain Park", March, 1979
  - Ligonier, "Administrative Review", August, 1971
  - Ligonier, "Computation of Non-Electoral Debt Limit Ligonier Borough January 1, 1974", January, 1974
  - Lititz, "Financing Municipal Government: A Study of Lititz Borough 1950-1957", April, 1957
  - Manor, "A Review of Manor Township Sewerage Needs", January, 1958
  - Marianna, "A Review of the Marianna Water Study", April, 1964
  - Masontown, "The Borough of Masontown Preliminary Sewage Survey", May, 1961
  - McCandless, "Financing and Sewage Service Rate Study of the McCandless Township Sanitary Authority", November, 1962
  - McCandless, "Home Rules Charter for the Town of McCandless Important You will Vote on this Charter", November, 1974
  - McCandless, "A Cost Analysis of the Proposed Home Rule Charter", October, 1974
  - McDonald, "Allegheny and Washington Counties Pennsylvania Feasibility Report Proposed Sanitary Sewage Works", May, 1965
  - McDonald, "A Police Pension Plan for Borough of McDonald", September, 1970
  - McKeesport, "Profile of Municipal Finances and Local Economic Trends", April, 1977
  - McKeesport, "A Financial Review for the First Nine Months of 1950 and Future Projection", October, 1950
  - McKeesport, "On the Brink of a Fiscal Crisis: A Review of McKeesport City's Finances 1971-1979", unknown
  - McKeesport, "General Fund Projection 1971-1972", December, 1970
  - McKeesport, "Fiscal Analysis City of McKeesport 1961-1965", January, 1967
  - McKeesport, "Alternative Fiscal Projections City of McKeesport 1971-1974", December, 1970
  - McKeesport, "Financial Analysis and Forecast 1955-1966", 1961
  - McKeesport, "Alternative Fiscal Projections City of McKeesport 1971-1975", December, 1970
  - McKeesport, "City of McKeesport Evaluation of 1972 Budget"
  - McKeesport, "A Revenue Code Account System for the City of McKeesport", January, 1975
  - McKeesport, "A Review of Present and Future Financial Needs", September, 1947
  - McKeesport, "City of McKeesport Insurance Study Interim Report", March, 1975
  - McKeesport, "A Progress Report on McKeesport's Design for Development", March, 1969
  - McKeesport, "Water Works Appraisal and Rate Study", October, 1948
  - McKeesport, "City of McKeesport and McKeesport Area School District Demographic and Fiscal Trends", October, 1977
  - McKeesport, "Report on an Analysis of the Rate Structure and Operating Costs of the Bureau of Water", September, 1944
  - McKeesport, "Report on an Analysis of the Rate Structure and Operating Costs of the Bureau of Water (Revised)", March, 1945
  - McKeesport, "Report on an Analysis of the Rate Structure and Operating Costs of the Bureau of Water", February, 1947
  - McKeesport, "Report on an Accounting System for the City of McKeesport Volume I Text, Volume II Exhibits", August 1943
  - McKeesport, "Report on the Personnel Study of the City of McKeesport", January, 1944
  - McKeesport, "A Procedure of Reports and Records of the City Garage", March, 1944
  - McKeesport, "Report on the Department of Public Property, Bureau of Sanitation", February, 1944
  - McKeesport, "Preliminary Confidential Report on a Financial Study of the City of McKeesport, Pennsylvania from 1937 to 1942", July, 1943
  - McKeesport, "Fiscal Analysis City of McKeesport", April, 1965
  - Mercer, "A Study of the Adequacy of the Sewage Disposal System of the Borough of Mercer to Meet Present and Near Future Needs", February, 1952
  - Mercer, "A Survey of Water Utility Fees for Billing Information", January, 1968
  - Millvale, "Borough of Millvale Police Pension Plan Self-Administered", September, 1958
  - Midland, "A Survey of Police-Related Services Provided by Midland Borough", February, 1974
  - Midland, "Financial Analysis of Midland Borough 1940-1944 and the 1945 Budget", May, 1945
  - Middlesex, "Municipal Employee Retirement System", December, 1966
  - Monaca, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications Borough of Monaca", September, 1967
  - Monessen, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection City of Monessen – 1968-1978", July, 1973
  - Monessen, "A Recommended Accounting System for the City of Monessen Vol. I Procedure", June, 1947
  - Monessen, "A Recommended Accounting System for the City of Monessen Vol. II Exhibits", June, 1947
  - Monessen, "An Approach to a Revenue Problem City and School District of Monessen", March 1953
  - Monessen, "A Fiscal Study of the City of Monessen", June, 1946
  - Monessen, "Preliminary Comments on the 1945 Budget City of Monessen", December, 1944
  - Monessen, "Financial Picture of the City of Monessen", June, 1944
  - Monessen, "Centralized Administration of Housing, Zoning, and Related Ordinances", February, 1958
  - Monessen, "City Finances in Monessen 1945-1955", October, 1955
  - Monessen, "A Report on Garbage and Refuse Collection in the City of Monessen", June, 1954
  - Monessen, "Selected Date on Libraries", February, 1958
  - Monessen, "Review of the Financial Position and Revenue System of the City of Monessen", August, 1958
  - Monessen, "A Health Officer for Monessen", April, 1957
  - Monessen, "Study of Monessen Fire Department", July, 1957
  - Monessen, "Review of the Recreation Program of Monessen", December, 1964
  - Monessen, "An Examination of Key Positions of the Operating Organization City of Monessen", February, 1963
  - Monessen, "The Municipal Income Tax City of Monessen", December, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Monongahela, "A Survey of the Accounting System of the City of Monongahela", January, 1958
  - Monongahela, "An Analysis of Short-Range Needs for Mass Transportation within the Mid-Monongahela Valley", May, 1977
  - Monongahela, "A Report on Playground Recreation for the City of Monongahela", December, 1948
  - Monongahela, "Proposed Position Classification Plan for Monongahela City", February, 1970
  - Monongahela, "Fiscal Analysis 1964-1968 and Projection 1969-1974 of the City of Monongahela", October, 1969
  - Monongahela, "A Survey of the Accounting System of the City of Monongahela", January, 1958
  - Morris, "Morris Township Financial Condition Survey", December, 1955
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Mt. Lebanon Accounting System Procedure Manual and Report of Progress", January, 1950
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Survey and Report for Revision of Pay Roll Procedures", July, 1955
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Pay Plan Proposal for Clerical/Technical Employees Municipality of Mt. Lebanon", March, 1981
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Review of the Improvement Assessment Liens", June, 1944
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Report on the Debt Retirement", February, 1947
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Township of Mt. Lebanon Report on Debt Retirement", June, 1949
  - Mt. Lebanon, "A Comparative Study of Municipal Professional Employee's Salaries and Fringe Benefits Prepared for Mt. Lebanon", July, 1977
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Township of Mt. Lebanon Accounting System (Manager's Office) Survey and Recommendations", December, 1948
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Survey of Accounting System Township (Manager's Office)", June, 1947
  - Mt. Lebanon, "Financial Analysis of Mt. Lebanon Township 1933-1943", December, 1943
  - Mount Pleasant, "Traffic and Parking Survey", June, 1957
  - Mount Pleasant, "Municipal Ownership and Operation of Off-Street Parking Facilities in Mount Pleasant Borough", September, 1960
  - Nanticoke, "A Report on 1960 Tentative Budget", December, 1959
  - Neville, "Sewer and Water Rate Study", April, 1971
  - Neville, "Review of Neville Township Sewer Fund", December, 1974
  - Neville, "Alternatives for Funding Improvements to Neville Township's Water Distribution System", May, 1976
  - Neville, "Sewer and Water Rate Study for Neville Township", May, 1975
  - Neville, "Fiscal Projections Water and Sewer Funds Neville Township 1970-1971", December, 1970
  - Neville, "Water Rate Study for Neville Township", December, 1978
  - Neville, "Analysis of the Fiscal Performance of the Neville Township Sewer Fund", June, 1979
  - Neville, "Neville Township Secretary's Accounting System Survey and Recommendations", March, 1948
  - Neville, "Neville Township Analysis of the Advertised 1948 Budget", May, 1948
  - Neville, "An Operating Study of the Water Department", September, 1948
  - Neville, "Administrative and Financial Survey of Neville Township Allegheny County Pennsylvania for the Years 1938-1944", October, 1945
  - Neville, "Review of 1955 Budget", May, 1955
  - Neville, "Survey of Financial Status of Neville Township as at December, 31, 1953", April, 1954
  - Neville, "Suggested Water Rates for Neville Township, Pennsylvania", August, 1958
  - Neville, "An Operating Study of the Water Department", March, 1962
  - New Brighton, "A Guide for Fiscal Planning", September, 1967
  - New Brighton, "Financial Analysis of New Brighton Borough 1963-1965 and 1966 Budget", October, 1966
  - New Brighton, "Financial Analysis of New Brighton Borough 1940-1944 and the 1945 Budget", October, 1945
  - New Brighton, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan", May, 1967
  - New Brighton, "Report on the Financial Operations in 1945 and the 1946 Budget of the New Brighton Borough", March, 1946
  - New Castle, "City of New Castle Electronic Data Processing Applications for Selected Municipal Functions", October, 1982
  - New Eagle, "An Analysis of the Financial Operations of the Borough of New Eagle", January, 1957
  - New Kensington, "The 1963 Financial Budget the 1962 Financial Operations", May, 1963
  - New Kensington, "City of New Kensington the 1962 Budget", June, 1962
  - New Kensington, "Recommendations Relating to the Accounting System", March, 1954
  - New Kensington, "A Financial Review with Recommendations for Financing an Improvement Program", March, 1950
  - New Kensington, "Analyss of Financial Operations of the City of New Kensington", December, 1958
  - New Kensington, "The Proposed Change in Real Estate Assessed Valuations for Tax Purposes", November, 1954
  - New Kensington, "The City of New Kensington Purposes a Solution to its Financial Difficulties", February, 1954
  - New Kensington, "Faces Another Financial Dilemma", December, 1953
  - New Kensington, "Recommendations Relating to the Accounting System of the City of New Kensington Volume II Procedure," March, 1954
  - New Kensington, "Financial Operations 1962-1963-1964", April, 1964
  - New Kensington, "Preliminary Survey 1970 Budget City of New Kensington", February, 1970